Guide to the Records of the Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs, Leslie Berlowitz 1970-1980 RG 9.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Study Groups Post-Conference Final reports, Jun 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Hamberger's Report on Undergrad Education, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Undergrad Studies Status Report, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Undergraduate Education Committee Members and Participants, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Underdraduate Education Conference, Nov 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Follow-up: Undergraduate Study, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Aims and Goals for Undergraduate Education, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Education Proposal, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Cantor Proposal Draft #2, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Undergraduate Conference, Jan 1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Workshop Reports/ Misc. extras, Apr 1977 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Post-Conference Meeting Leaders and JCS-LCT notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Instructions for the Physcial Arrangements Required for the Conference on General Education, Apr 1977 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Literacy, Jun 1976 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Notes of Meeting with Topic Reporters [LCT], Jun 1977 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Post-Conference Meetings with Deans/ LCT Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Social Understanding Recommendations, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - General Education Conference JCS Speech/Final, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Undergrad Ed. Materials, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Report of the Committee on Undergraduate Education, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate Education Study-Progress Meeting, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Copies of Culture and Civilization Final Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Study Organization Group Meeting-LCT Minutes, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Letters to Accompany Drafts of Report on Conference, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Study Group on Social Order Final report, Jun 1978 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - General Education Confernce Post-Conference Follow-up, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - General Education Study Meeting with Kosak-Timetable, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Language Study Group Final report, May 1978 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Mathematics Study Group Final Report, Jan 1978 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - For LCT- Study Group Final Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Study Group Reports-Complete, undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Moral Awareness Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Study on Undergraduate Education Organization Group Meeting, Dec 1977 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Womens Study Group Meeting Notes/Ideas, Mar 1976 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Womens Study Group Papers, Proposals, etc., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Womens Study Group Correspondance, etc., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Womens Studies Group Small Grant Application, undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Women in Higher Education Conference, undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Misc.LCT Notes, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227206 5
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs List and Lables, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Correspondance, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Interim Report, Oct 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #1, Feb 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #2, Apr 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #3, Jun 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #4, Jul 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #5, Oct 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #2, Dec 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Meeting #3, Mar 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Report of The Academic Affairs Committee Prepared for Judge Wienfeld, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Background for Meeting #3, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Extra Copies, Mar 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs Extras, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Budget Material for Continuing Education report, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - General Education Conference, Apr 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Roster-Completed Projects [Index to Research Materials], 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #1, Dec 1973 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #2, Apr 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #3, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #4, Apr 1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #5, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #6, Apr 1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #7, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #8, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #9, Mar 1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #10, Feb 1974 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #11, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #12, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Research Projects- OIRP #13, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - [Why Undergraduates Transfer to NYU], 1973 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Background on NYU [including list of honorary degree recipients, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 33)